Song:hanser
演唱：hanser
Lyricist & Composer:Yunomi
作词&作曲：Yunomi
Engine sound that seems to break Four
湛蓝的海水漾出的梦
Beyond the blue sea Five
好像那暖洋洋的天空
The passenger plane carrying the two
游荡在孤岛上空的云朵
Dare to crash land
嬉笑无助的你我
Swaying swaying lifeboat
左摇右晃的气垫船
Don't sink
也无力搁浅
I knocked up a wet skirt Ten
怎么办难道今生只能困在这里吗
Sandy beach spreading ocean
静静感受这轻柔的海风
No fan if you play alone
独自一人听着浪声放空
Sunshine warm
阳光洒满沙滩你向我走来
Premonition of love that bounces to the heart
我脸颊羞得通红
SOS to rescue team
写下大大的SOS
I can't see the rescue yet
顾自许下一起离开的Promise
Two uninhabited islands
在这只有二人的孤岛上
Holiday to spend forever
度过没有终止的Holiday
I want to dance with you
想要与你想要与你共歌舞一曲
South island
在南国的岛屿
Midsummer night twenty one
在盛夏夜晚里
I won't sleep until morning twenty two
夜以继日日以继夜不停地私语
For a ripe smell twenty three
伴着你声音
Wrapped twenty four
呼吸你的吐息
Dance floor One fruit twenty five
Dancefloor用单恋结下的果实
I'm sure it's sweet
也许会是苦涩的甘甜的
You cast a spell
乘船在施下魔法的梦里
Biting a dream
留下浅尝的痕迹
This heartbeat that seems to pop
快要蹦出的心跳声
The night sky echoes
振动了明闪闪的星辰
To you back to back
被璀璨夜空照耀着的我们
Don't realize
背靠着背无声
One or two flowing stars
偶尔划过的那一颗颗流星
I am looking for
点缀了梦境
Please, so that it will arrive someday
期待着这份爱恋某天能传达给你
Moonlight that guides the two
明月洒下了皎洁的Moonlight
I remember when I was little
照亮沙滩留下一片Wholewhite
I'm about to be swallowed by the darkness
忽然间想起曾经小时候
Frightened Lonely Night
惧怕黑暗的Lonelynight
It doesn't have to be inevitable
哪怕最终没有结果也好
You don't have to say forever
哪怕什么都没有说也好
But hey God, only now
可是我却无论如何都想要
I want to monopolize
独占你温暖怀抱
I want to dance with you
想要与你想要与你共歌舞一曲
South island
这南国的风息
Midsummer night
消散在盛夏里
I won't sleep until morning
夜以继日日以继夜不停地私语
Magic is not yet
那单恋的秘密
in the process of
却深藏在心底
Dance floor One fruit
Dancefloor用单恋结下的果实
I'm sure it's sweet
也许会是苦涩的甘甜的
You cast a spell
乘船在许下魔法的梦里
Biting a dream
留下轻咬的痕迹
Someday my love too
或许最后我的恋爱会是
I'm sure it's over
那苦涩的一场空一场梦
Until the sun rises again
但我仍想在最后的梦里
Let me dream
尝尽仅剩的甜蜜